Dr. Gordon Freeman





DOCTORAL RESEARCH

"Observation of Einstein-Podolsky-Rosen Entanglement on Supraquantum Structures by Induction Through Nonlinear Transuranic Crystal of Extremely Long Wavelength Pulse from Mode-Locked Source Array"

My research examined the use of ELW pulses from a mode-locked source array inducted through transuranic crystals to observe entanglement on supraquantum structures. Theoretical advancements included prediction of quantum resonance phenomena including the possibility of resonance cascades. I was motivated to conduct this doctoral research due to my passion for teleportation of matter and I believe I have laid the foundation for further experimental validation and development of practical outcomes.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CURRENT, FROM JAN 1995 (FT)

Black Mesa Research Facility Team Leader (Anomalous Materials)

As part of this promotion, I began conducting nuclear and subatomic research in the Anomalous Materials department. My team and I are particularly interested in dimensionality and its interaction with spacetime. The focus is on practical outcomes and applications in teleportation and communication with distal locations.

FEB 1991 – JAN 1995 (FT)

Black Mesa Research Facility Level 3 Research Associate

This position involved transitioning from purely theoretical work to experimental applications utilising the immense resources of Black Mesa. The transition required an initial learning curve in hazard containment, health and safety procedures and operating experimental infrastructure. Manipulating valves, carts, buttons, levers, etc considerably increased my physical fitness.

JUL 1982 - DEC 1984 (PT)

WashPests Limited Pest Control Technician

In this summer job I was tasked with helping eradicate pests from industrial areas. Work involved setting traps, spraying and physical eradication. I received praise for reaching difficult areas and my innovative use of a crowbar to assist in my work.

REFERENCES

Dr. Isaac Kleiner

POSITION Professor

EMPLOYER Department of Physics

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

EDUCATION

1986 – 1990 **Doctor of Philosophy**

Theoretical Physics

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

1985 Master of Science

FIRST CLASS HONOURS
Theoretical Physics

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

1982 – 1984 Bachelor of Physics

Department of Physics
The University of Washington

AWARDS

1985 Faculty of Science Masters Scholarship
Massachusetts Institute of Technology

1983 **Top Achiever Award – Physics** The University of Washington

COMPUTER SKILLS

BEGINNER Java, MS DOS

INTERMEDIATE Javascript, Python, HTML, CSS,

Microsoft Windows

Computer Hardware & Support

EXPERT Perl, Unix, LATEX

COMMUNICATION SKILLS

CONFERENCES Oral Presentation at the Annual MIT

Theoretical Physics Conference - 1987

POSTERS Poster at the Meeting of the American

Physical Society - 1985

SKILLS

Goal Oriented

I believe in action over long-winded discussions. I listen to everyone's viewpoints and use my judgement to immediately act based on consensus to achieve goals quickly and efficiently.

Physical Dexterity

Manual manipulation of experimental equipment and training within Black Mesa (e.g. the Hazard Course) have contributed to an enjoyment of working with my hands.

Passionate

I have been interested in theoretical physics such as quantum mechanics and relativity from an early age. My edu-

PHONE +1 (617) 253 1000 X5322 (Work)

MOBILE +I (232) 842-3583

Dr. Eli Vance

POSITION Scientist (HLI)

EMPLOYER Black Mesa Research Facility

EMAIL e.vance@bmrf.us

PHONE +I (800) 786-1410 x6235 (Work)

MOBILE +I (20I) 632-390I

cation and research have cemented this interest into a passion. I greatly enjoy carrying out fundamental physics research with potential practical applications.

PUBLICATIONS

Freeman, G. R. (1996). Chemistry of Multiply Charged Negative Molecular Ions and Clusters in the Gas Phase: Terrestrial and in Intense Galactic Magnetic Fields. *The Journal of Physical Chemistry*, 100(II), 433I-4338.

Jacobsen, F. M., Gee, N., **Freeman, G. R.** (1986). Electron mobility in liquid krypton as function of density, temperature, and electric field strength. *Physical Review A*, *34*(3): 2329-2335.

1996 doi:10.1021/jp951483+

1990 doi:10.1139/p90-097

1986 doi:10.1139/v86-297

1986 doi:10.1103/PhysRevA.34.2329

First author publications in **bold**